(Leonard:)So, Alex,
what's the topic of your dissertation?
(Alex:)I'm looking for Trojan asteroids
at Earth's L-5 Lagrange point.
(Leonard:)Oh. That happens to be Dr. Koothrappali's
field of expertise.
(Leonard:)You two have a lot to talk about.
(Alex:)Is that true?
(Alex:)- Is he all right?
- No.
(Leonard:)But compared to your boss,
he's the poster boy for sanity.
(Alex:)It's okay,
I've been around scientists all my life.
(Alex:)- My dad's an astronomer at SETI.
- Oh, SETI.
(Leonard:)The Search for
Extraterrestrial Intelligence.
(Leonard:)You should introduce him to Sheldon.
The search is over.
(Alex:)What kind of research are you doing?
- High-energy lasers.
- Ooh, military?
(Leonard:)Not yet, but I can remove unwanted hair
from 2 miles away.